A Guide to the Records of the Policy Office of Governor Mark R. Warner, 2002-2006
Library of Virginia
- V. Legal Files, 2002-2005 (accession 42412)., Extent: 2.45 cubic feet (7 boxes). (Box 247-253)
  - Subseries V.A. Attorney General Settlements, 2002-2005 (accession 42412) (Restricted: Closed for 75 years)., Extent: 1.75 cubic feet. (Box 247-251)
    - 2003
      - MCV Hospitals v. Warren Walker (Box 249, Folder 2)
      - UVA Medical Center v. Clarence A. and Barbara B. Bane (Box 249, Folder 2)
      - UVA Medical Center v. Robert Lee Cottoms, Jr. (Box 249, Folder 2)
      - MCV Hospitals v. Vanessa Castilan, Minor (Box 249, Folder 2)
      - MCV Hospitals v. Donald Lee (Box 249, Folder 2)
      - Commonwealth of Virginia, et al. v. Frank Solutions, Inc. (Box 249, Folder 2)
    - 2004
      - Warsaw Healthcare Center (Medicaid) (Box 249, Folder 3)
      - Regal Medical Supplies, Ltd. V. DMAS (Box 249, Folder 3)
      - Landsdowne Community Association (Box 249, Folder 3)
      - MCV Hospitals v. Timothy Amos (Box 249, Folder 3)
      - DMAS v. Benjamin A.L. Gatchel, minor (Box 249, Folder 3)
      - DMHMRSAS v. Catherine LoPresti (Box 249, Folder 3)
      - 7-Eleven, Inc. v. DEQ/SWCB (Box 249, Folder 3)
      - DMAS v. Estate of Keith Smith (Box 249, Folder 3)
      - UVA Medical Center v. Theodore and Celestine Johnson (Box 249, Folder 3)
      - UVA Medical Center v. Dietmar Weidenbach (Box 249, Folder 3)
      - UVA Medical Center v. George and Jane Quara (Box 249, Folder 4)
      - Holly Butler v. Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University (Box 249, Folder 4)
      - DMAS v. Retha M. Elam, deceased (Box 249, Folder 4)
      - VDOT v. Madjeski and Masters, Inc. (I-64 Bascule Bridge over the Southern Branch of the Elizabeth River) (Box 249, Folder 4)
      - Commonwealth of Virginia, ex rel. State Water Control Board now DEQ v. Sanitary Board of Bluefield and Sanitary Board of Bluefield, Inc. (Box 249, Folder 4)
      - Driggs Corporation v. VDOT (Route 288 and Route 76 [Powhite Parkway] Interchange) (Box 249, Folder 4)
      - United States Environmental Protection Agency v. Stone Container Corporation (Facility in West Point, Virginia) (Box 249, Folder 4)
      - Rose B. Murphy v. Robert C. Inman, III, et al. (VDOT) (Box 249, Folder 4)
      - UVA Medical Center v. Andrew P. Beirne, Jr. (Box 249, Folder 5)
      - UVA Medical Center v. Andrew Justin Thompson (Box 249, Folder 5)
      - United States Environmental Protection Agency v. Mirant Potomac River, LLC and Mirant Mid-Atlantic, LLC (Box 249, Folder 5)
      - GMU v. Dr. Bijan Jabbari and Isocore Corporation (Box 249, Folder 5)
      - ODU v. McKenzie Construction Corp. and McKenzie Construction Corp. v. ODU (Constant Hall renovations and additions) (Box 249, Folder 5)
      - MCV Hospitals v. Davin A. Wells (Box 249, Folder 5)
      - MCV Hospitals v. Shenickaw Ballard (Box 249, Folder 5)
      - MCV Hospitals v. John Abbott (Box 249, Folder 5)
      - DMAS v. Joshua Dingus (Box 250, Folder 1)
      - DMHMRSAS v. Julie Ann Raines Beagle (incompetent) (Box 250, Folder 1)
      - United States Environmental Protection Agency v. Stone Container Corporation (Box 250, Folder 1)
      - Schering-Plough Corporation (Box 250, Folder 1)
      - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University v. Neoreach, Inc. (Box 250, Folder 1)
      - Parke-Davis (Neurontin) Global Settlement (Box 250, Folder 1)
      - DMAS v. Estate of Charley Burton, Jr. (Box 250, Folder 1)
      - Virginia Workers' Compensation Commission Uninsured Employer's Fund v. James Howard (Box 250, Folder 1)
      - DMAS v. Patricia Brock (Box 250, Folder 1)
      - Virginia Workers' Compensation Commission Uninsured Employer's Fund v. Craddock Moving and Storage, Inc. (Box 250, Folder 1)
      - Virginia Workers' Compensation Commission Uninsured Employer's Fund v. McCarty and McCarty, Inc. (Box 250, Folder 1)
      - Diana Spencer, Administrator of the Estate of Louise Marguerite Warmoth v. Commonwealth of Virignia and Cheryl Stevens, R.N. (UVA Medical Center) (Box 250, Folder 1)
      - Mavis Lee Coffey Fitzgerald, Administrator of the Estate of C.R. Fitzgerald, deceased v. Commonwealth of Virginia, et al. (UVA Medical Center) (Box 250, Folder 1)
      - UVA Medical Center v. Maria Villanueva (Box 250, Folder 1)
      - Virginia Community College System, San Jose Construction Group, Inc., American Home Assurance Company, SmithGroup Midlantic, Inc. f/ka Tobey and Davis and McMullan and Associations (Box 250, Folder 2)
      - DMAS v. Bobby Akers (Box 250, Folder 2)
      - DMAS v. Estate of Samuel L. Warring (Box 250, Folder 2)
      - DMAS and Sun Healthcare Group (Box 250, Folder 2)
      - DMAS v. Crystal Thomas (Box 250, Folder 2)
      - DMAS v. Michael Pelton (Box 250, Folder 2)
      - DMAS and Alexandria Hospital, et al. (Box 250, Folder 2)
      - Lora Chapman, etc. v. Commonwealth of Virginia, et al. and Delia Pentecost, etc. v. Commonwealth of Virginia (both ODU) (Box 250, Folder 2)
      - UVA Medical Center v. Mr. and Mrs. Bobby W. Necsary (Box 250, Folder 2)
      - MCV Hospitals v. Earlene Melton (Box 250, Folder 2)
      - MCV Hospitals v. Omar Bailey (Box 250, Folder 3)
      - Sheila Lockridge v. Richard L. Hoag, Jr. (VDACS) (Box 250, Folder 3)
      - LandMark Design Group, Route 460/29 Interchange (VDOT) (Box 250, Folder 3)
      - Virginia Workers' Compensation Commission v. Watt e. Flippo, Jr. (Box 250, Folder 3)
      - VDOT v. Tidewater Skanska, Inc. (Box 250, Folder 3)
      - Commonwealth of Virginia (VDOC) v. Gilbane Building Company and Travelers Property Casualty Insurance Company (Wallens Ridge) (Box 250, Folder 3)
      - Virginia Worker's Compensation Commission Uninsured Fund v. Dan Johnson t/a Johnson's Bar-B-Que (Box 250, Folder 3)
      - Virginia Worker's Compensation Commission Uninsured Fund v. James T. Howard (Box 250, Folder 3)
      - VDOT v. Gannett Fleming, Inc. (Box 250, Folder 3)
      - Compromise by Virginia Small Business Financing Authority of Debt Settlement by Alpha Remanufacturing and M/M Sokos (Box 250, Folder 3)
      - Beverly Healthcare at Fredericksburg Nursing Home (Medicaid) (Box 250, Folder 3)
      - Suzanne deJanasz v. JMU (Box 250, Folder 4)
      - HCMF Corporation Civil Settlement (Medicaid) (Box 250, Folder 4)
      - Lewis Construction, Inc. v. VDOT (Box 250, Folder 4)
      - Manor Care Health Services, Alexandria (f/k/a Oak Meadow Nursing Home) (Medicaid) (Box 250, Folder 4)
      - VSBFA Guaranty Agreement Compromise, Warren Vanderpool, Jr. and Paul Vanderpool (Box 250, Folder 4)
      - Alease Jackson v. Commonwealth of Virginia and MCV Associated Physicians (Box 250, Folder 4)
      - VDOT and Allegheny Construction Company, Inc. (Routes 40 and 122 in Franklin County) (Box 250, Folder 4)
      - VDOT and APAC-Virginia, Inc. (Oceana Boulevard, Virginia Beach) (Box 250, Folder 4)
      - Access Ride (DMAS) (Box 250, Folder 4)
      - Odell Associates, Inc. (SCC Project, Tyler Building, Richmond) (Box 250, Folder 4)
      - Old Cannon Estate Road Salt Contamination (VDOT) (Box 250, Folder 4)
    - 2005
      - MCV Hospitals v. Olivia Davis (Box 250, Folder 5)
      - MCV Hospitals v. Andres Zueleta (Box 250, Folder 5)
      - Ruth Ellen Schooley v. Rusty Donald Lambert, et al. (Box 250, Folder 5)
      - Recovery by Commonwealth on the Division of Unclaimed Property's Claim in Allapattah Services, Inc., et al. v. Exxon Corporation (Box 250, Folder 5)
      - VDOT v. James Raymond Ellis Lee and Waste Management of Virginia, Inc., aka Chambers Waste Systems of Virginia, Inc. (Box 250, Folder 5)
      - DMAS v. Robert Ferguson (Box 250, Folder 5)
      - DMAS v. Robert B. Skogen (Box 250, Folder 5)
      - MCV Hospitals v. Rocco Pirrotta (Box 250, Folder 5)
      - MCV Hospitals v. Terri Johnson (Box 250, Folder 5)
      - GlaxoSmithKline (Medicaid) (Box 250, Folder 5)
      - Wireless E-911 Services Board and Ntelos, Inc. (Box 250, Folder 5)
      - VDOT and Jones Brothers, Inc. (Box 250, Folder 5)
      - PCL Civil Constructors, Inc. v. Commonwealth of Virginia (VDOT) (Box 251, Folder 1)
      - Serono, Inc./Serostim (Medicaid) (Box 251, Folder 1)
      - King Pharmaceuticals, Inc. (Medicaid) (Box 251, Folder 1)
      - DMAS v. Nicole Eddy, minor (Box 251, Folder 1)
      - DMA v. National Guard Bureau (Box 251, Folder 1)
      - MCV Hospitals v. Denise Elges (Box 251, Folder 1)
      - VDOT v. Cleco Corporation, Inc. (Route 18, Allegheny County) (Box 251, Folder 1)
      - VDOT v. Cleco Corporation, Inc. (four bridges in Page, Warren and Shenandoah Counties) (Box 251, Folder 1)
      - DGS v. Conquest, Moncure and Dunn, Inc. (construction of the Virginia Distribution Center in Henrico County) (Box 251, Folder 1)
      - MCV Hospitals v. Darleen James (Box 251, Folder 1)
      - MCV Hospitals v. Iehab Mohamed (Box 251, Folder 1)
      - MCV Hospitals v. Rosa Hernandez (Box 251, Folder 1)
      - MCV Hospitals v. Yneil Ellis (Box 251, Folder 1)
      - MCV Hospitals v. Jerry Eggleston (Box 251, Folder 1)
      - MCV Hospitals v. Joel Bautista (Box 251, Folder 1)
      - UVA Medical Center v. Mark Lucas (Box 251, Folder 1)
      - MCV Hospitals v. Robert T. White, Sr. (Box 251, Folder 1)
      - MCV Hospitals v. James McClanahan, III (Box 251, Folder 1)
      - MCV Hospitals v. Andre Alexander (Box 251, Folder 1)
      - DMAS v. Johnny Weaver (Box 251, Folder 1)
      - SWCB v. Newdunn and Newdunn v. SWCB (Box 251, Folder 2)
      - MCV Hospitals v. Erica Coleman (Box 251, Folder 2)
      - DMAS v. Robert J. Hill (Box 251, Folder 2)
      - MCV Hospitals v Glynis Watson-Toye (Box 251, Folder 2)
      - Tyler (SCC) Building Fire Alarm System (Box 251, Folder 2)
      - UVA Medical Center v. Leah Randall (Box 251, Folder 2)
      - Woodrow Wilson Rehabilitation Center v. David R. Forsch (Box 251, Folder 2)
      - Virginia Workers' Compensation Commission v. Thalmadge Wood (Box 251, Folder 2)
      - MCV Hospitals v. Donna Rose (Box 251, Folder 2)
      - MCV Hospitals v. James Ritenour (Box 251, Folder 2)
      - MCV Hospitals v. Jarvard Wright (Box 251, Folder 2)
      - VDOT v. Jacobs Civil, Inc. (Box 251, Folder 2)
      - VPI and SU v. The Gazette Group, Inc. (Box 251, Folder 2)
      - Marcellus Wright Cox and Smith Architects, P.C. v. The Rector and Visitors of Christopher Newport University, et al. (Box 251, Folder 2)
      - DMAS v. Gabriella Valentino, minor (Box 251, Folder 2)
      - Commonwealth of Virginia and Virginia Turf Management Associates, Inc. v. Mary Susan Resoulte, t/a All Pro Services (Box 251, Folder 2)
      - Woodrow Wilson Rehabilitation Center v. Johnny Carver (Box 251, Folder 3)
      - Securities litigation involving UVA and Safety-Kleen Corporation (Box 251, Folder 3)
      - McGee's Crane Rental v. DCR (Bear Creek Lake) (Box 251, Folder 3)
      - Gambro State Civil Settlement Agreement (Medicaid) (Box 251, Folder 3)
      - VDOT v. Louis Berger Group, Inc. and T.Y. Lin International (Danville Bypass) (Box 251, Folder 3)
      - Terry Roop and Cheryl Roop v. Donald Scott Glenn (Virginia State Police) (Box 251, Folder 3)
      - Harry Woodrow Ryan and Virginia State Police (Box 251, Folder 3)
      - Teresa Tan v. Commonwealth of Virginia and David W. Nelson, M.D. (VCU/MCV) (Box 251, Folder 4)
      - Shriver and Holland Associates, Inc. v Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, et al. (Box 251, Folder 4)
      - Securities litigation involving UVA and Safety-Kleen Corporation (Box 251, Folder 4)
      - DMAS v. Adrianne Wright-Bent (Box 251, Folder 4)
      - MCV Hospitals v. Bennico C. Cooper (Box 251, Folder 4)
      - MCV Hospitals v. Timothy D'Angiolillo (Box 251, Folder 4)
      - MCV Hospitals v. Tina Markwick (Box 251, Folder 4)
      - MCV Hospitals v. Antoinette Lewis (Box 251, Folder 4)
      - MCV Hospitals v. Michael Johnson (Box 251, Folder 4)
      - James E. Sellman, M.D. dispute with DMAS (Box 251, Folder 4)
      - VDOT v. Service Electric Corporation (Box 251, Folder 4)
      - DMAS v. Debora Foxx (Box 251, Folder 4)
      - Betty Walls v. VDOT and DTH Contract Services (Box 251, Folder 4)
      - Karin Ann Stretchko v. Ted Clough and VDOT (Box 251, Folder 4)
      - MCV Hospitals v. Sanchez Paige (Box 251, Folder 5)
      - DMHMRSAS v. Ashby T. Berry (Box 251, Folder 5)
      - Home Care Supply (Medicaid) (Box 251, Folder 5)
      - MCV Hospitals v. Raymond Price (Box 251, Folder 5)
      - MCV Hospitals v. Juan Cruz (Box 251, Folder 5)
      - VCCS and States Roofing Corporation (Box 251, Folder 5)
      - DMAS v. Daniel Dean (Box 251, Folder 5)
      - Safeco Insurance Company of American and Golden Eagle Construction Company, Inc. v. VDOT (Lee Chapel Road, Fairfax County) (Box 251, Folder 5)
      - Charles Mark Cosslett v. Virginia State Police (Box 251, Folder 5)
      - DMAS v. Dominique Miller, minor (Box 251, Folder 5)
      - Nancy C. Fink v. Commonwealth (DMHMRSAS Catawba Hospital) (Box 251, Folder 5)
      - Joyce E. Taylor v. Commonwealth (UVA Health System) (Box 251, Folder 5)
      - DMAS v. William "Ray" Copney (Box 251, Folder 5)
  - Subseries V.B. Interstate Agreements on Detainers, 2002-2005 (accession 42412)., Extent: 2 folders. (Box 252)
    This subseries is housed in 2 folders and is arranged in reverse chronological order by year. The Interstate Agreements on Detainers subseries documents the requests from other states for the temporary transfer of custody of prisoners within the Virginia correctional system to other jurisdictions for trial. Subseries contains requests to the Office of the Attorney General, completed Agreement on Detainers forms submitted by requesting jurisdiction, and supporting documentation (copy of arrest warrant, mug shot, etc.).
    - (Box 252, Folder 1)
    - (Box 252, Folder 2)
  - Subseries V.C. Service of Process on the Governor, 2002-2005 (accession 42412)., Extent: 0.70 cu. ft. (Box 252-253)
    This subseries is housed in two boxes and is arranged in reverse chronological order by year. The Service of Process subseries contains legal documents received by the Governor's Policy Office and routing memorandums from Counselor to the Governor (Robert M. Blue, 2002-2005 and Robert P. Crouch, 2005) to the Office of the Attorney General.
    - 2005 (Box 252, Folder 3)
    - 2005 (Box 252, Folder 4)
    - 2005 (Box 252, Folder 5)
    - 2005 (Box 253, Folder 1)
    - 2004 (Box 253, Folder 2)
    - 2003 (Box 253, Folder 3)
    - 2003 (Box 253, Folder 4)
    - 2002 (Box 253, Folder 5)